<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rahul Rameshbabu</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Rahul Rameshbabu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:23:18 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://binary-eater.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 19:35:45 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am an open source enthusiast mainly interested in low-level programming and operating systems. My personal interests are mainly in PC-class development and improving the personal computing space in the open source community. On my free time, I mess around with input devices and the stacks related to them.
For fun, I have worked on the hid-nvidia-shield driver. I started this project after playing some games with a friend and learning that Xbox controllers had first class haptics support on Linux (thanks to the xpad driver made by individuals) while the NVIDIA SHIELD controller I was using did not.</description></item><item><title>Site theme change</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/theme_change/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 18:23:18 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/theme_change/</guid><description>Why I changed the theme of my site? When I first started this page, I built my own theme hugo-theme-ghci based on the work done on the hugo-theme-ghci theme. I did this because I dislike the idea of using someone else&amp;#39;s creative work to express myself on a personal site. I am really thankful to people who share themes for this purpose. I just thought back then I could make something more creative that expresses my interests.</description></item><item><title>The Tunnel to Summer, the Exit of Goodbyes</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/tunnel_to_summer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 12:44:22 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/tunnel_to_summer/</guid><description>Natsu e no Tonneru, Sayonara no Deguchi Original work written by
Hachimoku Mei and illustrated by
Kukka The movie was directed by
Tomohisa Taguchi (Bleach: TYBW) Starring
Ouji Suzuka as Touno Kaoru Iitoyo Marie as Hanashiro Anzu Hatanaka Tasuku as Kaga Shouhei Komiya Arisa as Kawasaki Koharu Terui Haruka as Hanamoto-sensei Koyama Rikiya as Touno&amp;#39;s father Touno Karen as Touno Karen Produced by
Ryoichiro Matsuo Just for some background, I was out of the country on a business trip and recently returned.</description></item><item><title>Personal Setup</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/personal-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:22:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/personal-setup/</guid><description>Goal of this page This page will contain information on my setup I use for open-source and personal development. This includes both the software and physical sides. Normally, I do not think setups are worth discussing. However, I do think there is something to be gained in this specific case since I currently do not use normal or &amp;#34;out of the box&amp;#34; gear + software stack. Listed below are some of the highlights in my setup that will be expanded on in the near future.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/description/</guid><description>I am a programmer primarily focused on delving into kernel-space programming.
My secondary interests are programming languages and related concepts.
I enjoy doing work that generates truly &amp;#34;free&amp;#34; software.</description></item></channel></rss>