<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Binary-Eater: A developer focused on low-level programming</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Binary-Eater: A developer focused on low-level programming</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:56:16 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://binary-eater.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Site Tweaks</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/site-tweaks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:56:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/site-tweaks/</guid><description>Currently, the site uses hugo-theme-ghci for its functionality and style choices. This page is used to present shortcomings that seem to arise from the design and potentially solutions for addressing them.
Enhancement ideas Currently, inter-page navigation is non-existent
This is especially problematic considering that the homepage does not load immediately but animates Traditional navigation mechanisms found in typical websites feel clunky to me
Would want to implement a context switcher similar to GitHub&amp;#39;s or Slack&amp;#39;s implementation</description></item><item><title>Haskell From Zero</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/haskell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:51:18 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/haskell/</guid><description>Plans for this page I have started to self-teach myself Haskell. The experience has been interesting. A lot of effort to really delve deep into the fpl and type theory concepts. I took two programming language courses in my undergrad. One course was taught in OCaml, while the other involved the K framework. However, I still found my learning journey to be a non-trivial but fun one. I unfortunately did not get the opportunity to take the course under Professor Mattox A.</description></item><item><title>Spacemacs</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/spacemacs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:50:57 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/spacemacs/</guid><description>Plans for this page Spacemacs is my editor all the time. I use it for text editing but also use it for tasks beyond programming. Like a number of other things on this site, I was introduced to spacemacs by Professor Mattox A. Beckman. My plan is to write about the features I use and delve into my .spacemacs a bit.</description></item><item><title>Org Moding My Life</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/org-mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:50:15 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/org-mode/</guid><description>Goal of this page I really enjoy using org mode. Professor Mattox A. Beckman from UIUC got me into using org. Since then, I have been using org for driving just about everything in my personal and professional life. Even the content of this site is written using org mode. The goal of this page is to share some of the things I enjoy in org that others may enjoy.</description></item><item><title>Nix</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/nix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:38:42 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/nix/</guid><description>Goal of this page I think the way Nix approaches package management is brilliant. nix-shell is an amazing tool for handling dependency specification of a project in a way that supports diverging from the system libraries and components. I learned about NixOS from Professor Mattox A. Beckman.
I plan to write content about the things I like in nix and NixOS.</description></item><item><title>Personal Setup</title><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/personal-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 19:22:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/posts/personal-setup/</guid><description>Goal of this page This page will contain information on my setup I use for open-source and personal development. This includes both the software and physical sides. Normally, I do not think setups are worth discussing. However, I do think there is something to be gained in this specific case since I currently do not use normal or &amp;#34;out of the box&amp;#34; gear + software stack. Listed below are some of the highlights in my setup that will be expanded on in the near future.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://binary-eater.github.io/description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://binary-eater.github.io/description/</guid><description>I am a programmer primarily focused on delving into kernel-space programming.
My secondary interests are programming languages and related concepts.
I enjoy doing work that generates truly &amp;#34;free&amp;#34; software.</description></item></channel></rss>